Could this have happened
while we were sleeping?
To me and Giorno?
Mista and Trish?
What kind of messed up
voodoo crap is this?
Last I checked, people's minds
couldn't just trade bodies?
Stay your hands for now!
Wait, that can't be a stand!
Is that Zipperman?
Ain't no doubt!
It's Bucciarati!
In my eyes,
I'm going to turn back on my head.
I'm going
to
turn back on my head.
Nessun può Star un destino scelto,
Roman solo il risultato,
che voi sarete distrutti.
L 'eterna Zoom esiste solo per me,
puoi cantare canzoni di
trastezza nel Monday senza tempo.
Oh, thank God!
Glad to have you back!
You even beat the boss to the
punch and tracked down the arrow!
I know that cadence.
That's how Narancia
speaks, if memory serves.
Am I right?
Huh? Yeah!
Thought so. And you two?
I'm Giorno.
And I'm Trish.
Impressive work, Bucciarati.
It appears you've already
pieced together what happened.
Wait a minute...
Are you the man we were
supposed to meet with?
I am Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
I died by Diavolo's hand.
However, after switching
souls with this turtle,
I was able to maintain a presence here?
like a ghost might haunt
the plane of the living.
And that over there is my stand.
With the Eros' power, he was
transformed into Chariot Requiem.
He is responsible for our displaced souls.
Wait,
if my soul's in this body, then it's only
natural to conclude the boss is inside.
Yeah, don't worry about
him, he hasn't moved at all.
Guy's sleeping like a baby.
Might you be, Mista?
Yeah, I'm really glad to
see you're okay, old buddy.
Anyway, number seven's
got his eye on your body.
If it's so much as twitches,
we'll know immediately.
Again, he's out cold.
Might be a while before he gets up.
Bucciarati!
Chariot Requiem's back on his feet!
We've already learned
how to use the arrow.
If we can just grab it,
this'll all be over!
What's this, Zippermann?
What are you doing?
Quick, the arrow!
Requiem's going for it!
Not on my watch, you little bitch.
No, wait, something's wrong.
Miseria, did he?
I'm gonna kill you, you stupid ass!
That thick skull of yours is about to
become holier than a dog shit-eating priest!
The pillar next to you! Mesa! Doc!
Spicy lady!
Die, you bastard!
I'm gonna blast your
ugly head open and paint
the streets with your
chunky noodle juices!
You'll number one cut the shit out!
What the hell do you think
you're doing, you moron?
Hey, stop it!
Huh?
What was I doing?
What happened?
It can't be!
Guys! Over there!
Requiem!
He's going for the arrow!
We can't just let him take it!
Oh, you gotta be freaking kidding me!
How did all that just happen?
If I were to guess,
It's a result of his frenetic state.
Not even I have seen chariots show
such terrifying powers before.
But this much is clear.
In response to my subconscious
will, he's become a defensive stand.
As long as he lives, he'll
allow no one to touch the arrow.
To turn stands against their users.
Such a cunning defense mechanism
will prove challenging to defeat.
So not only can the arrow control all
our minds, it can pull tricks like this?
How are we supposed to get at it?
Dude is out of control!
Sure,
our stands might be supercharged,
but that just means if we try to grab the
arrow right now, we'll get roasted alive!
Bad Benedict!
No howling! You pipe down!
Oh, there, there.
It'll be okay.
Hey, Mista!
Something's making number
seven lose his barbles!
Whoever's inside, Bucciarati,
they're coming too!
My god, is it him?
We can worry about the arrow later.
Get into place and don't
take your eyes off him!
Now, Mista, take a shot and make it count!
What did I say?
Put those bullets of yours to work!
Yeah, I heard.
But, dude, did you forget that's
your body I'd be shooting at?
There's no need to worry.
Golden Wind can patch up
bullet wounds without effort.
So, shoot.
All we gotta do is incapacitate him.
That was your plan, right, Bucerati?
Guys, he's on the move!
Come on, let's get him!
That should do it, fellas!
I don't think he'll be
charging at us any time soon!
No one's showing up on my radar!
Looks like there won't be
any backup to deal with.
We did it!
Once we get the arrow,
this'll all be over.
And then, when we're back in
Napoli, it's off to school.
Hot damn, I'm already psyched.
The first thing I'll do is stuff my
face with an authentic margarita slice.
Might even top it with porcini's.
After that...
If I ever see Fugo again, he can
call me a kagakatsu all he wants.
I won't give two shits.
And even though Bakio's gone...
Trish!
I'll protect you till my dying breath!
That's a promise!
Narancia...
Mista, just to be safe,
take out both of his legs.
Uh, yeah, sure.
Hey Trish, would you mind
handing me my bullets?
I want them all.
Just reach down into
my boot and grab them.
Uh, okay. Okay.
Hey, pick up the pace, will ya?
Those legs won't shoot themselves.
Wait, hold on a sec.
Time jumped, just now.
We skipped a few seconds.
I know, the bullets
that fell on the ground.
Did anyone actually hear them land?
It can't be.
I was watching him closely.
Not once did I catch him move,
let alone evoke Emperor Crimson.
It just doesn't make any sense.
What other nefarious forces could
possibly be haunting us this time?
Listen, Trish.
I might need a little favor.
Could you go ahead and drop
one more bullet for me?
Oh, come on! Are you deaf?
Can you even count how many of them
are rolling around there right now?
The answer's four!
The absolute freaking worst!
I can't have that bullshit
number anywhere near me!
If they fell while you
were handing them over,
then for the love of God, do me
a solid and drop another one!
How sure are we exactly?
That's Diavolo in there.
Hey Trish, could you just remind me again?
When we all woke up, you said you
couldn't sense the boss anywhere,
isn't that right?
Well, what about now?
Are you picking up anything at all?
That cannot be the case!
You swapped with Narancia, and
accordingly Mista swapped with Trish.
It stands to reason Buterati
swapped with Diavolo.
With Requiem's powers, they're
the only pairings that work.
Yeah, I get what you're saying, but none
of that explains why time just jumped.
That can only mean whoever's in that
body right now can't possibly be Diavolo.
Narancia, how does our perimeter look?
Are you able to detect anyone coming?
Narancia?
Please, I'm begging you.
Just one more bullet,
please just drop one more.
You're driving me back.
What the hell?
Why couldn't I feel a
soul like I usually do?
It doesn't make any sense.
Out of the way! Move!
Let me through! Now!
Dammit, no!
That's impossible!
How on earth could he have?
Match, scan the area right now!
Make sure there's no one around!
Narancia!
Butcherati!
Hurry up and get him down from there!
Don't just leave him like that!
Do something, goddammit!
You need to settle down!
Let me handle this!
Please stay focused and
keep your gun at the ready!
He'll attack again.
We have to find him before he does, quick!
Go, Zipperman!
Heal him!
Pull those jam bars out of
there and get to work now!
The people outside the
Coliseum are waking up.
So where is he?
I can't sense him at all.
It's like he's gone.
What else could have happened?
There's no way in hell he'd
just up and vanish like that.
Emperor Crimson's range is
two or three meters at most.
How then did he attack
us from way over there?
Well, all right. You did it.
Naraj is awake.
Welcome back, you little bastard.
How are you feeling?
Jeez, you really scared us.
I'm sorry, Nista.
There's no one left in here.
It's empty.
The physical wounds he
suffered have healed.
But still, Golden Wind
couldn't get to him in time.
He was...
He was already gone.
But I'm just...
Not here.
His form it's just an
empty vessel now I can't
find him his soul has
left there's nothing here?
Try as I might I can't
bring him back I wasn't
fast enough my soul could
just slip right back
in if it wanted it could
inhabit both bodies
without a problem not
even one he's that empty.
It was all so sudden.
None of us could have guessed.
No!
That bastard, where could he be hiding?
This should never have happened.
The only explanation is if
there were two Diavolos.
Wait, the child that appeared before him.
Could it be?
Were both of them one physical
body with two different souls?
Butcherati, I got it.
Diavolo must have two personalities.
That is the only possible answer.
The one currently inside your body
is the young man I met earlier.
He and Diavolo may share a physical
body, but their souls are separate.
The human soul can be a
strange and delicate thing.
A traumatic childhood event
can easily fissure it.
As the individual grows, so too do
the fissures until the soul is split.
Over time,
the second personality distinguishes
itself from the original,
with one of them soon becoming dominant.
It's a well-documented disorder.
Listen to me.
What I'm saying is no mere conjecture.
Reports from across Europe
confirm that even one's
physical form will change as
the personalities alternate.
Requiem managed to extract these two
souls from the singular body they share.
One of them, the young man's,
found its way into Buterati's body.
The other one, however,
for reasons unknown has established
itself in a body we haven't found
that's how diavolo took us by
surprise we didn't think he'd still be
roaming around in a different
vessel this shit hurts my head two
personalities so that's what the boss
has been hiding as we speak countless
civilians are awakening the haystack
will soon grow intractably large
I'm certain he'll pounce on us again
and this time he'll finish the job
that's one scenario however it's
just as likely he's nowhere near us
right now diavolo wants the arrow too
which is why narancia was the first
one targeted he's blinded us we've
lost our only radar it's enabling
him to move about freely no one can
track him not with lil bomber anyway
yes but even so you must keep your
focus on the arrow there's no point
in going after emperor crimson
without its power that's precisely why
we need to locate requiem before he
does do you remember which way he
went to the west he's left a trail
of people regaining consciousness in
his wake wait a minute are you really
planning to chase him down right
now what about your mangled body back
there i avoided his vital organs?
He'll live, but he's not
getting up anytime soon.
I made sure of that.
Stay put, okay?
You'll be safe here.
I won't let anyone hurt you again.
I promise.
And don't you worry, when it's
over we'll bring you home.
Watch out for anybody
coming near us. Let's go!
Trish what are you doing stay close right
Hey baby!
You're under arrest!
Come here and let me show you
how these cuffs look on you!
Hey!
Is everything alright back there?
Yep.
Just a false alarm.
This guy rushed at me so
I thought he was the boss.
But it was just a dumbass cop.
It's become increasingly clear to me.
Requiem has neither directional
nor emotional objectives.
Though we've closed in on him, he
hasn't once turned to look at me.
There's no question
he's a living organism.
Even if the resemblance he bears to some
rubber figurine would suggest otherwise.
In his mind I've yet to
even register as a threat,
but even if I did he can
barely throw a punch.
Still his physical presence is quite real.
I mean he's been seen
and touched hasn't he?
it's no good can't even get close it's not
just our stands anything we throw at it
it sends flying right back in our faces
this arrow might really be untouchable it
doesn't matter how hard you try to reach
for it it's gonna push you back with just
as much force and here he comes again How
are we supposed to pick
this damn thing up?
It's like it's mocking us.
Hey, Requiem won't allow stand
users to pick up the arrow.
Which leads me to think,
what if a person without the gift
were to go ahead and try their luck?
Would they succeed?
Well, what are your thoughts?
What do I look like, a stand scientist?
How the hell should I know?
Hey, guys!
Look, over here!
I've been reduced to a reptile
fighting to hold on to its dear soul.
That means I'm no longer a stand user.
It can't repel me.
Mista!
The time has come!
Take the arrow and infill your stand now!
We are the power who'll see the future.
Cause we are the fighters
just fighting for a ride!
Thank you.